http://www.ncwine.org/privacy

WineriesEventsRegionsMountainsPiedmontCoastWine TrailsxPrivacy PolicyThe North Carolina Department of Agriculture & Consumer Services is committed to protecting your privacy on this website.We collect personal information from our visitors on a voluntary basis only. Personal information may include name, address, phone number, email address and other relevant data. We do not require this personal information to obtain access to most of our site.We do, however, require it in order to properly respond or to fulfill requests for the following:Brochures or other mailed informationEmail newslettersSharing your opinions through surveysUsing Contact Us for correspondenceWhen you contact us via email, we will only use the information to respond to your request. We may occasionally redirect your message to another government agency or person who is in a better position to answer your question.Public DisclosureThe personal information we request is used by us in order to process a request for information by you or for marketing our products or services. We do not collect, track, sell or rent personal information to other organizations.If you provided us with personal information through this web site, you have the option to request that we not contact you in the future. Information about you or your requests will not be shared with any other organizations.What Information Do We Collect?Our web servers collect the domain names, but not the e-mail addresses, of visitors to our website. This information is aggregated to measure number of visits, average time spent on the site, pages viewed, and other relevant statistics.We collect the following information:The Internet domain and IP address from which you access our siteThe date and time you access our siteThe length of time you spend on our siteThe pages you visitThe URL of the site you came from, if applicableWe collect this information to measure the use of our site, to improve the content of our site, to evaluate technical performance and to identify problem areas. There also may be tracking pixels on the site that collect additional data.CookiesTo enhance your experience on our site, many of our web pages use cookies. Cookies are small text files that we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your email address or other personal information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at our site. Once you choose to provide a web page with personal information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. A cookie is like an identification card. It is unique to your computer and can only be read by the server that gave it to you.We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience on our web pages (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to our site). We also may use cookies to provide you tailored offers of products and services. Cookies are essential to the proper functioning of NCWine.org.If you want to control which cookies you accept, you can configure your browser to accept all cookies or to alert you every time a website’s server offers a cookie. Most browsers automatically accept cookies. You can set your browser option so that you will not receive cookies and you can also delete existing cookies from your browser.DisclaimerThe North Carolina Department of Agriculture & Consumer Services has compiled content and information contained in this site based on data provided by local tourism partners and business entities. While every effort is made to ensure the accuracy of this information, the North Carolina Department of Agriculture & Consumer Services makes no representations, guarantees or warranties as to the accuracy, completeness or suitability of the information provided on this web site. All data is subject to change without notice. Travelers are advised to contact individual businesses or organizations to obtain the most current information before traveling.Additionally, content on some pages of this site is submitted and owned by tourism and business entities in North Carolina and is not the property of NCWine.org. It is the responsibility of those partners submitting content to secure and manage rights to said content. The North Carolina Department of Agriculture & Consumer Services is not liable for the misuse or rights violations of partner-submitted content on those pages, but will assist in facilitating contact with said partner(s) if you believe materials violate copyright rights, per the directions below. In select other cases, imagery, video and other content is sourced from industry partners, with confirmation that said partners have rights to those assets; in those cases, The North Carolina Department of Agriculture & Consumer Services will direct copyright inquiries to the appropriate party.If you believe any materials accessible on or from NCWine.org infringe your copyright rights, you may request removal of such content (or access thereto) by submitting a request to whit.winslow@ncagr.gov with identification of the copyrighted work that you believe to be infringed. Please describe the work, and where possible include a copy or the location (e.g., URL) of an authorized version of the work.The NCWine.org website contains links to other sites and we attempt to only link to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy. Links to third-party websites are provided as a convenience for our site visitors and do not constitute endorsement or control of their content.Copyright©2017 North Carolina Department of Agriculture & Consumer ServicesContact InformationAdditional questions or concerns about these policies should be directed to The North Carolina Department of Agriculture & Consumer Services.About NC WineAmerican Viticultural AreasCompetition WinnersNorth Carolina Winery GuideMediaIndustry Resources877-3NC-WINE© 2020 North Carolina Department of Agriculture & Consumer Services  |  Privacy PolicyXWineriesEventsSite
